Thank you for watching.
And now, it's time for our host, Bananaman, to welcome you to Nogizaka Construction Workshops!
Good morning, Nogizaka-chan!
Jersey jersey jersey!
Everybody's wearing jerseys.
Oh!
Male
That's great!
Ken Matsudaira's Matsuyama Sanban
You really have a worker's taste, don't you?
What should we do?
Decide, Mr. Matsudaira!
Unite with the new captain!
Yay!
My dream is to be in the 4th or 5th term
The third captain of Super Axe
Minamina Umezawa
We challenge a project to shorten the distance with the junior students at once.
Tonight, she'll be working with the 4th term students
and challenge the past game challenges again!
We aim to break all records!
That's why we made a special order for their jerseys!
Because, you know, it stands out, doesn't it?
That guy...
Ume Wiz Nogizaka Houta
Yay!
And if you fail in your assignment
Only the captain will take responsibility
You'll have to drink the Butt Drink 2023 series
I'll be doing this all week and all next week.
I'm gonna puke if I don't succeed.
Oh, no!
Are you okay, 4th term?
Yes, I'm fine.
The 4th term is still a dream...
Do they talk a lot?
They talk.
We talk and talk.
But none of them are that close to each other.
That's not true.
I see.
Yes, I do.
That's not true.
You're the new captain all of a sudden.
What are you going to do?
If things get weird...
Stop it!
Let's get to it... let's go!
Toss batting in succession!
Yay, yay, yay!
We challenged the best member project.
Aiming for 5 consecutive hits
Toss batting challenge
Last time
We succeeded!
This time, five fourth-term students and Umezawa
We're aiming for a new record!
What should we do?
Who has experience?
No one.
I heard someone has experience.
I hope they'll take it all the way to the plums.
There are six of us.
I'm sure you can do it.
Here's the batting order.
We'll connect to Umezawa and see if we all get a hit.
If Endo fails, we've already failed.
That's right.
We've got to hit it.
As long as you hit it, you're good.
Endo, you're holding the bat like that.
Just a little bit.
Hold it short, hold it short!
You can read and listen too.
I'll be right there.
I'll be right next time... and first time too.
You'll have to decide at the end.
Do you think I should go first?
Why?
Should I pull something?
No, no, from this point of view...
I don't know...
I'm leading him by the nose.
He's a superstar!
He's a superstar.
He's doing it for Hanako.
We've got one major leaguer
No, of course not
I think Rust is good
All right, let's go for it.
Let's go!
Let the continuous toss batting begin!
Scary.
That's good. That's good.
Shuño!
Sanctisse!Sanctish it!
Pop batter's end.
A clean swing and a miss.
Easily failed challenge!
Try again.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's more.
Well, I'm sorry, but I'm going to have to include one failure and a penalty drink.
Pink.
Pink Ranchu!
So, the penalty drink for the captain is the new pink one!
Thank you for the 2023 Pink!
Isn't it beautiful?
No, it's very smooth.
It's my first time.
Gau gau gau pink, please.
Ew.
Ew!
It's so good!
This is...
It's a drink made from pickled plums
It's a drink made from pickled plums and vinegar.
Because it's made from plums and vinegar.
It's already ume.
It's a special plum drink.
Wait a minute, everyone's in the mood for another round, but it's over.
No, that's right.
We've been told by the staff to stop one more time.
Let's do it one more time.
Oh, no!
So, as a favor to you, we'll have Umeza as the pop-up hitter, and we'll do the crying sign challenge.
Yes... after I'm here...
I'm sure you can tell by looking at him.
Bad link to Mr. Kimura!
I'm sorry... but I don't like pink.
You guys shouldn't say negative things about Nogizaka because they're going to be a new group that's going to make a big leap forward.
Hama, come on, Pink.
Pow!
I feel bad!
That's why I'm gonna guess! I'm gonna hit it!
I'll hit it rather than hit it!
Last chance!
Will the new captain and I unite our hearts and make it 6 in a row?
We can do it!
What the hell! Why is the downside already over?
Why can't we hit it!
Hey...
Captain Umezawa took careful aim.
He didn't give it to the juniors by his own musings!
New Batsu drink!
Oh no!
Damn!
I'm so sad!
But there's always the next one.
Next time, we'll have to liven it up.
You don't have to type, right?
Okay.
Next game, Mr. Himura, please.
Bench press plus.
Yes!
This is another project with the best members.
Five of us lifted a barbell weighing a total of 110 kilograms.
Last time, we lost.
We challenged the same record again this time.
Will the five of us work together to clear the record?
We did it, didn't we? We did it!
You were able to lift 20 last time, weren't you?
I think it was the 5 that failed.
We'll have to think of a way to make the 20 a little shorter.
Whoever can do it can do it.
I'm confident.
I can lift up to two people in the chair section.
That's amazing.
What do you mean "two people"?
I've lifted two people.
I was lifting two people.
I'm going to chop it down to 22.54 people, 20 kilos, one person.
And just so you know, this is just one challenge.
Oh, I see.
Okay, who's going to go first?
I'll go first.
Here we go.
It'll be a disaster if Ume doesn't make it.
I'll take that one.
Okay, ume, this is 22.5.
I'm going to start with your chest down.
And up, straight up at the elbow.
That's the clear condition.
I see.
Here you go, Ume.
Umezawa cleared 20 kilos last time. Can you lift 2.5 kilos?
All right.
He's trafficking.
Here you go.Here we go.
Here we go.
Yay!
Ume nice.
Excellent.
22.5 kilos clear. Heavy?
I'm heavy. I was going to give it to you. I think I'm going to have to drink it.
I don't want to drink anymore.
Next, Tamura attempted 22.5 kilos!
22.5 kilos. I thought it would be harder than I thought.
Really? That's not the same as 20 kilos?
I don't think so.
If you did 22.5, you'll do 20.
That's big... to lift 22.5 kilos.
Tamura, are you okay? My cell phone just came on.
Oh, Mike.
Mike's a little busy.
Here comes Tamura's challenge, 22.5 kilos.
Here we go.
If he fails, he'll be out of the record books.
Can Tamura lift 22.5 kilos?
Go for it!
22.5.
Here we go!
Here it comes, here it comes!
Did you just say "okay"?
I'm sorry, I'm just trying to be supportive.
Oh, really?
No, I was letting go of you when you just came up.
Are you okay?
No, no, no, just now.
Because it was a close call.
I made a few adjustments.
But you were going up at the end.
I did.
Himura-san, you raised Shuro's price.
Take a good look, Mr. Himura.
It was like this at the end.
In the middle... in the middle...
It's dangerous.
That's not quite right.
What's next?
I'll go.
I said, "What are we going to do?" We'll take 20 each.
Twenty is fine.
20 per person.
So, in other words, two 22.5s.
I'll take care of it.
Me, too. I'm not sure how much I weigh.
Yeah. - Yeah.
What are you doing?
Janga-janga.
Janga janga janga.
So the confident Sehmiya
22.5 kilograms.
What was Sehmiya doing?
She was doing mechanical gymnastics.
Mechanical gymnastics?
I'm the most nervous I've been this year.
The most nervous I've been all year.
It hasn't been that long.
Actually, it's not March.
It's the end of January.
Come on, Semya 22.5.
The pressure of a one-shot deal.
Let's see if Sameer can make it to the next one.
Come on.
Come on, stop him.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Yes, sir.
Please.
Okay. Excellent. It's heavy.
No problem. Here, here, this muscle.
And Matsuoka, do this here, and clear the last 20 kilometers.
I'll do this for sure!
Good luck!
I'd be scared if I had to lift two cheerleaders.
Wait a minute. These girls make mistakes.
Please don't. You'll be fine.
Matsuo, who's done cheerleading before... will she be able to do it?
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
You're all right. That's good.
Now we have 20 kilometers to go. I'll be fine.
I think I'm okay. I have a lot of muscle.
So much muscle!
The last time this happened, four of us worked together to lift 90 kilos.
For the first time, even the last man is deciding.
Can Shibata overcome the pressure and lift 20 kg for the new captain?
Here we go!
Let's go!
Aaaaah!
Clear!
Yay!
Age Press class cleared!
You did it, Ume! You did it!We did it, didn't we?
After all, if we work together, we can do it.
Flower Stage
A well-known event in the show where the contestants try to see how many people they can get on a round platform.
This time, we challenged to break the record set during the Nogi Floor days. If 14 people could get on the platform and hold it for 5 seconds within the time limit of 3 minutes, it would be a new record.
The last time we did this, there were 13 people on the stage.
That's amazing!
The last time we did it was in 2012.
2012, that's 11 years ago.
So, what's the plan?
But I'll go to the center.
The center.
I'm sure you're right.
Okay, then.
Okay.
Okay, let's see if we can clear the hole stage for 14 people.
Let's go! Ume's in the middle.
That's a small stage.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
7 people
8 persons
8 people
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
Nine.
Eight.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'll hold you tight.
I'm okay with one person.
One and one and one and one and one.
Wait a minute... who's the last one?
I'm in the entertainment business.
Let me know when you're alone.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Twelve.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Fail.
There's still time.
How many times can you try if you have less than 3 minutes?
Two more minutes. Two more minutes.
We have time.
Slowly, slowly, slowly...
Here we go.
Come on, opposite side.
The other side?
It's so stable.
One.
One to go.
End, end, end.
We're at 13.
Oh, no!
Oh no!
Oh, no! So close!
One more person off-balance, and it's too close to call!
Can the 14 of us become one with one minute left?
It's not too late, it's not too late, it's not too late!
2 minutes elapsed... 2 minutes elapsed...
We can do it! We can do it!
Wait, what?
Come on, come on, come on.
Maybe we should rebuild it again.
I can do it. I can do it.
Wait a minute.
I'm in, I'm in, I'm in.
End of the line, end of the line, end of the line.
End hand, end hand...
54321.
Goal!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
I'm in.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
Oh, my God.
Nice, nice.
You guys are awesome!
Wow, this is great!
I could hear them saying, "This way, this way, this way," and it made me want to cry.
That's right.
That's great.
It's true.
It's amazing.
When the endo gets on at the end, he doesn't get on anymore.
Endo...
And Kuromi was falling all over the place.
Kuromi-sensei...
He was just standing there in the middle? Ume and others...
He had all kinds of people in his grasp.
This is Nogizaka46.
No, it's true.
This is it.
You know...
I counted down louder than on New Year's Eve.
Oh, no!
I did!
Louder than New Year's Eve
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Isrilay time attackChair Relay Time Attack
The most exciting competition in chairland, the chair relay, was held over the chairs in the studio.
The first person lays out 10 chairs, and the second and third person make a lap around the course in caster chairs.
The fourth person is trying to set a new record for the time it takes to clear all the chairs.
The goal is to beat the previous record by 58 seconds!
Fifty-eight seconds!
What do you want me to do with it, in that order?
What's the order? Have you ever rolled over a chair?
I have.
Well, I do a lot of it in class, so...
It doesn't matter if we do it in class.
Why don't you go to class?
Last time, Kakki and I were in charge of carrying chairs.
So the chair-bearers are still here.
Isn't that a good name?
That's what they call it.
We'll set a new record by having the best chair carriers in the world.
We have 10 chairs.
Can we split them in half?
Only if we start there.
No, last time...
No, no, no. Last time, we had a go-between at the start of the race.
That or high school.
Yes, sir.
Okay, that's good.
I remember you well.
That's the new ship.
I'm not sure if you want me to sit in second.
How was it last time?
I was sitting.
Then it's okay.
Okay, let's go.
Chair Relay Time Attack.
Ready.
Let's do it.
Yay!
Oh, that's how you do it.
Cutty's almost there.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Oh, shit.
We're losing time.
Tacky.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Come on.
It's okay.
All right.
Go, go, go.
You're late. You're late.
Swon, you're late.
Let's see if the one in the back can go.
Can the back one go?
Too slow, too slow.
Slow, slow, slow.
You're slow. - You're slow.
Too slow, too slow. You're too slow.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go.
Go, go, go
One more. One more.
One more.
Put the top one in, then.
Oh, I got it.
No, this is a little...
I think Kurumi was braking.
Kurumi!
Even lining up the first persimmon...
It took a while to line up the first persimmon.
Atvia, the persimmon was the first to go.
No way. Panic.
Kurumi was running very slowly and gracefully.
What was the record?
What was the time?
Aha!
1 minute and 04 seconds!
Wow!
But I didn't expect that.
Wow, that was close.
No, Black Sea, you definitely should have gone backwards.
Backwards, backwards, backwards.
So...
Plum x Drink.
There it is!
Today's third drink for Captain Umezawa is
Light green, the new color for spring!
You look like a guy drinking tequila on the beach.
It's true, isn't it?
You're a real party person.
Party people!
Let's go, let's go!
Let's go.
Oh!Ah!
Peek.
It stopped. It stopped.
It stopped already.
What's this?
Wasabi juice concentrate.
I love wasabi.
That's why...
I use it up in a week or so.
Seriously.
So you're totally fine with this?
That's why.
I'm not going crazy around here, am I?
New captain likes wasabi.
Write it down, write it down.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It's the first time for Kakki too.
I spent a lot of time away from them.
I see... I see...
I didn't expect you to be so quick.
Yeah, I was early.
I was early.
I felt like I was on a bullet train.
Kuromi.
Why didn't you go to the back?
I was going so far back.
I've never done it before.
We're in the middle of a business.
Why did you do it in the middle of the business?
That's why
It's the end of the series.
The fourth series...
If there's anything you want to do...
If there's something you want to do...
I'll do it this way.
We can definitely go for this one.
We can switch the members around.
But if you want to go with this group...
If you want to go with this group...
I'll ask him to switch.
He's the one who said that.
Can Umezawa and the 4th term members become one?
What'll you do?
I'll go first.
Line them up.
Then Kakki and Saya take the chairs, and Kuromi last.
Kuromi last.
I close it.
Is there any way to open it?
I have some knowledge...
Excuse me...
I have some knowledge.
The last chair, just before the tiles.
Yes, yes, yes.
I like it.
I can see the wood coming together.
It's amazing how thick it can get.
It's good.
Finally, the final challenge!
Will we set a new record?
Okay, here we go.
That's so cool.
Here we go.
Can you beat 58 seconds?
Here we go!
Yeah!
That was fast!
I can do it. I can do it.
I'm going fast!
I can go!
I can do it!
Imano-san's looking good.
What's he checking, Konno-san?
He's early.
Quick! Quick! Quick!
This, this, this.
It's okay. It's okay.
OK, OK, OK
This, this, this
Ouch.
Come on.
You're so fast
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it
dangerous
put it away, put it away
ah!
Ikeke!
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
not in yet not in yet not in yet not in yet not in yet
ooh ooh ooh ooh
There it is
Well, the chair was a little out at the end...
The current time
59.8 seconds.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
That was close.
Like that last one, the black one.Like that last one, black.
↑up
wow!
Oh, no!
You can cut it down to less than a second... if you keep doing that last cone.
Wow, that was close. That was close.
[fast forward]
Wow, this is really bad.
But you did a great job.
I know, I know, I know. Next week we'll get closer to the 5th period.
Yay!
The bonus package for "Hito wa Yume wo Taisetsumu" has been decided!
Tickets for the graduation ceremony of Ayane Suzuki will be on sale from March 21
10 chu-phrases?
Japanese, math, science, social studies, what's your favorite?
Thank you very much!
Please subscribe to our channel!